Evil comes in all sizes.
Puppet Master is a horror, fantasy, science fiction
film directed by David Schmoeller.
After being contacted by their mysterious former colleague, four psychics arrive at a
secluded hotel where they are stalked by a group of murderous puppets.
Alex Whitaker, played by Paul Le Mat.
Andre Toulon, played by William Hickey.
Dana Hadley, played by Irene Miracle.
Neil Gallagher, played by Jimmie F. Skaggs.
Megan Gallagher, played by Robin Frates.
Frank Forrester, played by Matt Roe.
Puppet Master (also titled The Puppet Master and Puppetmaster) is a 1989
American horror film written by Charles Band and Kenneth J.
Hall, and directed by David Schmoeller.
The film stars Paul Le Mat, Irene Miracle, Matt Roe and Kathryn O'Reilly as psychics who are
plotted against by a former colleague, using puppets animated by an Egyptian spell.
Originally intended for summer 1989 theatrical release, before being released on home video the following September, Puppet Master was ultimately pushed to
a direct-to-video release on October 12, 1989, as Band felt this was likely to be more financially successful than the theatrical market.
It was very popular and has since developed a large cult
following, and an extensive franchise.
The film explores themes of puppet, murder, old dark
house, dark fairy tale, mysticism.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.